Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained every treasure
that the world had to offer.
Smiling, even as he stood upon the scaffold,
he issued a challenge to the world.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
Now those who dare to dream hoist their
flags and sail into the great pirate era.
Don't be here, don't be here.
I'm late, I'm late.
1, 2, 3, shine, you, we come!
Don't let your wall, break
up, roll up, roll up!
I'm going to go with a
sweep from the jump start.
If you're going to go without a world,
1 2 3 Shine 1 2 3 Shine
We go!
Brother, it's too hard to dig here.
Of course it is.
This island is all rocks and tree roots.
No, don't bury us.
We're victims too.
Please, I'll do anything you want.
Just let me live. Captain Luffy.
No, I mean Black.
He made us do this
Listen, I have a secret to share with you.
We didn't give a damn about going
to the new world with the Straw Hats
The reason we joined
Was so we could stab them
in the back and collect
their bounties without them
ever suspecting a thing?
Oh, I won't let my friend die! Oh, God!
Take that, bastard!
Huh?
Uh-oh.
That's weird. Whoa!
And sure,
your Straw Hat did look a little off,
but it had been two years,
so I didn't think much of it.
You lied without remorse, and deception
is a sin, one that you will be buried for.
Brother, how goes the grave?
I'm digging! I'm digging!
Sinners all, these poor fools.
Gods in heaven, please forgive them.
Grant them peace and death. Yes! No!
Peace, yes, but not death!
Still, it's not all bad, I suppose.
I did find the real Luffy.
I told you there wasn't
any choice in the matter.
What did you expect?
Dark King Rayleigh was there.
He's as strong as Kizaru.
Even with the pacifistas, we
couldn't so much as slow him down.
Unfortunately, the Caribou Brothers
escaped along with the rest of their crew.
It seems they took some of the
fake Straw Hats with them as well,
though I can't imagine why.
At any rate, we captured
most of the pirates,
even though the real Straw Hats
heavily damaged two of our pacifistas.
One of the units was the same
prototype they fought before.
Its strength hasn't changed
in the last two years.
That's bad news. For us.
I don't know what they've been up to,
but the Straw Hats are immeasurably
more dangerous than before.
Tell the Marines in the New World that
they have a new threat coming their way.
The Straw Hats have returned, and they're
stronger than we could have imagined.
A pity they had to take off so soon.
But I'm proud of them.
They're tough.
They're gonna do just fine!
You were watching?
Yes, I'm a big fan!
I know that smile, Ray.
What's on your mind?
Huh?
Ah
It's nothing, really.
Whoa! Oh!
Hey, that's a nice ship you got there.
Thanks, but it's not exactly mine.
Rather, I stole it after
my house burned down.
Oh, yeah?
And what's your name?
Rayleigh.
My name's Roger.
It's destiny meeting you, I say. Oh, yeah?
How about we team up and turn
this whole world upside down? Huh?
And I thought I drank too much.
I don't know who you are or what
you're selling, but I'm not interested.
Come on!
Before then, I never
believed much in fate.
But maybe nothing really
happens by accident.
We're just too blind to see all the signs.
Anyway, that hat found the right man.
So long as it sails,
I'll stay here, waiting.
Because I want to see a
new king before I die.
The surface is already so far away.
What a view!
I've been under before, but
portholes on a submarine?
They got nothing on this!
We're sinking! Sinking!
What if we get a leak?
This is freaking me out!
Yeah, it feels like we're
leaving the whole world behind.
It's eerie. No big deal.
I've done this like a
bajillion times before.
It's cool.
Nope, not pooping my pants at all here!
The ocean sure is awesome!
Look at that!
They really are trees, huh?
Wow, I totally forgot about that!
They're giant mangroves.
You can't tell when you're up top,
but it's sure quite a sight
to see from down here.
The majesty of nature is truly humbling!
Why, my eyes would be
popping out of my skull!
If I had any eyes to speak of, I mean.
Who cares? I've seen this.
Because you got on the
wrong ship! Shut up!
Don't ruin this for us!
These roots, they're beautiful.
And think about it.
They stretch all the way down
to the bottom of the sea.
Okay, you win.
Hey, Chopper, I think there's
something behind that tree. Huh?
Whoa!
It's huge!
Took us long enough to get here.
But whatever, it was worth the wait.
I wonder what comes next?
Oh, fishies!
I bet I didn't grab them!
I see.
These look pretty good, too.
Here goes.
That's not funny!
If you put that bubble and we all
die, I'm gonna kill you! Twice!
Nami, you know how the
coding works, right?
Can we get some basic tips before
another idiot flips out on us?
Good point, okay Rayleigh gave me
a manual, but I can summarize it.
So listen closely, okay?
It's real!
I can die happy!
You're such a king!
You don't have to take us with you!
Who's flipping out now, idiot?
What?!
His nosebleed shot out! I see.
It maintains its shape well.
You'd think that it would burst,
Especially considering
the immense amount of
water pressure the coating
must be exposed to.
How nice.
And I thought we'd all drown down
here, never to be seen again.
Salty!
Get out of here!
Bright seawater, dammit!
Pull up for me!
Ah, gee, what the heck
happened to you back there?
I knew you were weak to pretty
girls, but this is a real liability.
You're supposed to be cool.
That poor man.
I can only imagine the horrors he must
have endured during the past two years.
Let's hope he lives long enough to see
the mermaids he was so looking forward to.
Uh,
and let's also hope they aren't quite so
lovely that the sight of
them strikes him dead.
When we get there, we'll have
to ask for blood donations.
But they won't be human.
I hope fishmen have the
same kind of blood as him.
So,
Sunny's coating has the same
properties as the bubbles on Sabaody,
meaning that objects or people can pass in
and out without causing
it any harm at all.
Spare me the bubble science!
We got a man down here!
Sanji aside, she's not wrong.
We saw this all over Sabaody.
It only stretches so far, then
allows an object to pass through.
So the good news is if we get
attacked by any nasty sea creatures,
We can still fire cannons at them just
like we would if we were above water!
Wait, so what would pop it?
Is it that durable?
It does fine with single objects,
but if too many things pass
through at once then it'll break.
Let's see like if a sea king clamps down
on the ship for example, that's bad.
Also the coating doesn't protect the
ship from anything except water so if
we crash into a rock or a trench and
the mast breaks or something like that
then the bubble could also burst so
it's not like we can just bounce around
down here still as long as we take the
usual precautions we should be fine.
I mean I'm sure Luffy will try to get
us all killed but what else is new.
So we're in clear.
After all, good.
Well, in theory at least.
But a lot of ships try
to make the trip to Fish
Man Island and over 70
percent of them sink.
We are so dead.
One Gum-Gum gatling and I bet I can
catch all the fish swimming out there.
Yeah, if I cut enough holes in this bubble
thing I bet I could catch even more.
Aren't you listening to Nami?
That's too many holes.
Our chances down here?
are bad enough as it is!
Oh, break your bones!
Let's fix them!
Let's break them again!
No fair!
Haji said he'd show us the Fishman Island?
Like it was no big deal, And now
we're stuck in this death bubble!
slowly descending to our demise! Oh, yeah!
Lunch time!
They packed a bunch of food for me!
Since Sanji's sick, we should
have ourselves a Pikmin!
Yay!
All that screaming made me hungry!
Oh, and I'm wasting away! Cool.
As long as Nami thinks
the ship will stay stable,
We don't have to steer it or
anything right now, do we?
Nope.
We'll just be cruising on the sea
current till we get further down.
So, yeah.
I'm sure we'll have more
excitement a bit later.
But for the time being, we might as
well just kick back and take it easy.
Well, I wouldn't call this
taking it easy, exactly.
But there's something you guys should
probably know before we reach Fishman Island.
It's so much surprise!
You got all kinds of secrets, don't you?
Can you transform into a tank?
Oh, wait, maybe?
You've got laser guns!
Tell us, Robo-Pro!
Super-armored! Me.
Sorry, no new secrets.
Secrets inaccessible, Robo.
He speaks robot!
OK, I know robots are cool.
But listen up.
Or eat and listen, if you like.
Like Usopp said,
Hachi was supposed to show us the
way to Fishman Island himself,
but he got hurt real bad back on Sabo Odi.
He came down here ahead of
us to get medical treatment.
Anyway, it was the same
thing that happened to Duval.
Meaning, he was protecting the
Sunny from anyone who came for it.
Things got ugly about a year ago when the
Navy found out the ship was docked there.
Both him and Duval got
taken out in a big fight.
Huh?
Wait, a year?
Then who was protecting
the Sunny after that?
We had one more secret ally.
If not really, then who?
Someone who separated us two
years ago, for better or worse.
The Warlord. Huh?
Turns out Bartholomew Kuma was
on our side the whole time.
A few days back.
When I made it to the Sunny,
I couldn't believe my eyes.
He was right there.
I've been waiting for you.
What the hell are you doing here?
Mission accomplished.
You saw for yourself, there wasn't
a single scratch on the Sunny.
Later, Rayleigh gave me the whole story.
I am a member of the Revolutionary Army.
If it's within my power, I want to
help the Straw Hats escape from here.
You guys probably knew that something
was up, but now we know the truth.
He saved the Sunny,
and he saved our lives.
And then, after we were
sent flying from the island,
Kuma paid Rayleigh a visit
and dropped another bombshell.
I don't have much time.
Not as myself.
The details are a little
sketchy, But evidently,
Kuma surrendered his body to the Navy.
They used him as an experiment and
replaced his body parts one by one.
By the time the War of
the Best rolled around,
his personality had been
completely erased. Wait,
he knew where he sent us, but he didn't
know what we'd do once we got there,
and that we would even make it back.
And you said his personality was taken
away, but he still protected the Sunny?
The guy who worked on him is
this dude named Dr. Vegapunk,
And Kuma must have made
a deal with him because
he programmed one final
mission into his brain.
Defend the Thousand Sunny
from any attackers until
the moment that a Straw
Hat returns to claim it.
So even though he's been reduced
to a living weapon with no memory,
he's been carrying out his own orders,
protecting our ship for the past
two years to fulfill his last wish.
But why?
He barely knew us.
I mean, why'd it matter
to him? I don't know.
Maybe it's cause of Luffy.
You said Kuma was part of
the Revolutionary Army,
and Luffy's dad was the
leader of those guys, right?
I don't know much about my dad,
but it seems like that robot
bear dude was a good guy,
so he can't be too bad if they're friends.
Kuma.
The bottom line is,
our survival and all the things we
accomplished in the past two years,
we owe to him.
Whatever his reason was,
we should be grateful.
And we may never find out the truth,
because it's not like we can ask
him to explain himself anymore.
all we can do now is
honor his memory and know
that Bartholomew Kuma
was our greatest ally
until he took his last breath as a human.
Unfortunately, we'll
never be able to thank
him since he'll just be a weapon and
likely our enemy the next time we meet.
That's all I wanted to say.
Kind of a lot to work through
all at once, isn't it?
Someday.
I hope we can at least find
out the rest of the story.
Kuma saved us, huh?
Oh, you're awake. Good. Have some lunch.
It's from Amazon Lily.
Oh, Amazon Lily.
The island with all the women.
Of course that's where he sent you.
Do you know where I was
these past two years?
Because I'm kind of thinking Kuma's
not such a good friend after all.
In fact, if he were here right now,
I'd like to kick his metal face in!
Now, now, Sanji.
We've all had our share of troubles.
Before I became a pop music
sensation, I was trapped in a cage.
Still, the only thing that matters
now is the voyage awaiting us.
You don't know, man!
You don't know anything!
Straight ahead!
Brother, look!
It's them! I know.
Like you said, they're straight ahead.
You think I'm blind?
Looks like we'll be sailing
with the Straw Hats after all.
Wow, how far down are we?
I don't know, but it's
getting darker and darker.
We passed the photic zone,
and it looks like we're around
the bottom of the aphotic zone.
About a thousand meters, give or take.
It's quiet, and the sunny
itself feels oddly still.
It's almost like floating in the sky
Wait a sec, what is that thing a fish?
No, are you ready?
We only get one shot at this
Before you say anything, I
know what you're thinking.
Just shoot them and they'll all drown.
They're wanted dead or alive, after all.
So why not let them die?
Well, that would do it all.
Because the Navy wouldn't
know who killed them.
We have to deliver their heads
personally on a silver platter.
Then they will fear us.
The whole world will do our strength.
We'll take them out before they suspect.
My big smiling face is the last thing
they'll see before they die! Yes, sir!
Uh, right there!
Hey, you guys, there's a ship-looking
thing coming our way. What? You sure?
Why don't you come look for yourself?
Charge!
It's a pilot ship!
They're ramming straight into us!
Go away, you morons!
You're going to make us all drown!
They're not trying to break our ship.
They're trying to board it!
Dummies, who are they?
Run!
Hard to board, now!
Attack them, CJ!
Oh, tenacious, aren't they? That sound...
They don't know when to quit.
Who are these guys after?
The bubble's about to pop!
Keep it up, sea cow! Yeah!
You think they want to board the ship?
Sea cow?
I know that noise from somewhere.
The two bubbles are touching!
This is a big moment, brother! Good!
Is everybody ready?
Yeah!
Mama, it's me!
We've met before!
You're from the Arlong Pirates, right?
Do you remember me? Nami!
I was at Arlong Park!
Hey, Luffy, doesn't that
thing look kind of familiar?
I don't know.
Dump-pump pistol!
Let's pay our new friends
a visit, shall we?
Hey, that guy's up to something!
Stay out of my car!
Guess he's looking for a fight, then.
There's no time to waste!
Follow my lead!
Fools!
They're completely dumbfounded.
If they're gonna sit there
catching flies Then we'll strike
while the iron is hot We'll
smite this entire crew Right now
For glory
Come along men We'll make
the beggars for mercy?
What's wrong Skull? Don't panic.
That's not good.
We left Captain Tribe
on the ship back there.
Now it's time for a little greeting!
Fire the Gatling gun!
Men, shower them in bullets!
I want every last one of them dead!
Send these Straw Hats.
THE HELL!
Huh?
No! Wait!
You're not going to throw
me into the water, are you?
Please don't do that to me, my friend!
I'm begging you!
Come on!
You're a reasonable fellow, are you not?
By the way, you're very good-looking!
I'm sure someone like you understands
the value of human life, right?
Emphasize!
The gods are watching!
You'll be judged for this!
Oh, make up your freaking mind already!
Weren't you just about to fire your Gatling
gun and blast us all to kingdom come?
Me? No!
I was just, uh, I was just joking around!
I ain't laughing.
Anyway, tell me.
I know you're the captain of
that ship, but what's your name?
That's Roro no Azoro!
Uh, don't be ridiculous.
What in the world makes you
think I would be the captain?
I'm, uh, oh!
Those ruffians were keeping
me as a, a slave! That's it!
Boy, ooh, glad that's over!
Say, how's this?
Do you think I could stay on this nice
ship with you all for a little while?
Huh? Please?
Wow, I feel kind of sorry
for this poor loser.
He's obviously lying! Are you crazy?
What? Seriously?
Hey, I have a question.
Where'd that giant sea cow
pulling your ship come from?
Hello.
Oh, my.
Who's this vixen?
I take it you're the famous cat burglar.
Oh, watch it, pal.
Nobody's allowed to drool over our
beautiful navigator except for me.
Don't worry.
You're perfectly...
Hey, it's getting really old.
Cut it out.
The sea cow?
Who knows?
I just happened to catch it
out in the ocean somewhere.
When you're underwater,
having a sea monster pull your ship
is the mark of an experienced captain.
Huh? Awesome!
Stop it, sea cow!
What's the problem?
Brother!
We're on our way to rescue you!
I'm gonna find a sea monster, too!
What crazy ideas are
you hatching now, Luffy?
We should try to rehabilitate him
with something a little less sexy.
Hey, Nami,
the direction we're taking isn't exactly
the same way the Log Pose is pointing.
Oh, no problem.
The correct course is technically
southwest, so we're in the clear.
Yeah, but if we went in a straight line,
we could get there a whole
lot faster, couldn't we?
Well, if you go straight, you risk
getting swept away in a sea current.
And if that should happen, you might run
into an underwater mountain or a volcano,
see?
That's why.
Huh? Yikes!
I'm with you on this one.
Yeah, but I thought all the
currents here were dangerous.
It is the Grand Line, after all.
So are you saying that some
of them are actually stable?
Well, this one is.
That should do it.
Now you stay put. Hey!
It's gonna start getting
colder from here on out,
so make sure you put
on a coat or something.
You bring up a good point.
I'm already starting to
feel goosebumps on my skin.
Well, except for I...
You don't have any skin
because you're a skeleton.
Chopper, skull jokes are
the only thing I have.
Please don't take that away from me.
We're going somewhere
cold, not the deep sea.
Don't you guys know the
water's cold in the deep sea?
It's just like a bathtub.
Hot water rises and cold
sinks to the bottom.
Oh, does it?
It won't take very many baths. Aha,
because heat rises and
there's not much sunlight,
so there's nothing to
heat the water down here.
The temperature's not the only thing
that's different at the bottom.
you're not still depressed
are you once we move
down we'll find something
called deep currents
you don't run into them terribly often but
they're much larger than
the regular currents also
they're quite unique in that their flow is
completely independent of
what you see closer to the
surface currents under
the currents and you even
have a diagram huh you
sure do know a lot of stuff
that's because I'm so
old not only that but
all currents are connected
to each other but
that doesn't mean they have to flow in the
same direction they flow
east west up and down
it's like a big long dragon all
tangled up the deep currents tend to
travel at a surprisingly slow pace
after they reach the deep sea it takes
approximately 2 000 years before
they finally make their way up to the
surface of the water that makes me
feel young again actually two thousand
Yes, 2,000.
And because of that,
there are countless tales about what
lurks within those deep, dark currents.
Monsters.
Curses.
The Wrath of the Undead.
You mean the deep sea is haunted? What?
The sea's haunted? Help!
That sounds fun to me!
Calm down, guys.
I don't know anything
about the wrath of the
undead or whatever you're
freaking out about,
but I do know that we'll encounter
or a downward-flowing current soon.
Once we do, we should be able to
ride it down into the deep sea.
She said something
about deep-sea currents.
I don't know.
You morons can at least
pretend like you understand me.
Shall we sing a duet, Nami? Shut up.
It's here.
Nami, I see it. Really?
Shut up!
Whoa, that's freaking sweet!
Whoa! Amazing!
Admit, whatever that thing
is, it's pretty cool.
This one's called the Downward Plume.
Whoa!
It's almost like a giant waterfall!
Except underwater!
The sea is, like, falling into the sea,
Which doesn't make sense, but I like it!
It's going so fast!
Mother Nature, you're one crazy lady.
What a spectacular sight.
And from the looks of it, I'd
say the stream runs fairly deep.
I've heard stories about these currents,
but they do not do them justice.
It's crazy dark down there!
The floor so far you can't even see it!
We're dead!
At this speed, we're going to get pile
driven straight down to the bottom!
Are you sure it's safe if
we just go with the flow?
If you're worried about
the ship, don't be.
Sunny was built from
the treasure tree, Adam.
It's as tough as they come.
Oh, is that crap?
Someone really does live down here.
It's no legend.
A demon that rules over the deep seas.
The enemy of all mankind.
Please listen to me, Straw Hats.
We have to turn back!
We're gonna die! Oh, yeah.
I forgot you were here.
There's a sea monster!
Jeez, what is the matter with you guys?
Just spit it out.
It's here.
It's the Kraken!
A legendary giant octopus monster!
He made fish food out of those ships.
They left for the new
world and never made it.
Turn around, please!
I'm not ready to die!
I beg you!
Just wait around for a couple
days and it'll probably go away!
Hey, shut up for a sec!
I just had a perfect idea! Yeah! Guys!
We just have to capture it!
I'll let you know.
Do you know what I'm talking about?